Have you ever been asked to do something, and then given no guidelines
你是否曾被要求做某个东西 但对方未给你任何说明
on what it should look like or what you should include?
比如最终的效果应该是怎样的 或者你应该在其中包含什么？
Imagine if you'd asked the Udacity ask you to complete a project and
假设优达学城让你完成一个项目 但是
gave you no free break.
没给你任何指示
I'm sure that would be frustrating.
我想你一定会感觉无从下手
Knowing what the employer wants gives you direction in your application, and
所以 了解雇主的期望可以为你的求职申请指明方向
will make it easier for you to edit your resume and prepare for the interview.
让你更有的放矢地编辑简历和为面试做准备
You want to be someone who can perform the necessary job functions, and
你要具备所需的岗位职能 并
help drive the mission and goals of the company.
帮助驱动公司的使命和目标
The best employee not only has the technical proficiencies, but passion for
最优秀的员工不仅要技术娴熟 还要对他们所从事的工作
the job they're doing.
充满热情
Take Udacity, everyone who works at Udacity is passionate about education.
就拿优达学城来说 每个在优达工作的人都热爱教育事业
Even if you are a leader in your field if you aren't interested in
即使你是自己领域的佼佼者 如果你对教育不感兴趣
education you'll not be a good fit for this company.
那就不适合这个公司
Let's walk through how you would find out what the employer is looking for and
我们来讲讲你如何找到雇主的期望 以及
how you can communicate that in your application.
如何在简历中传达你满足这些期望
I'm currently on the jobs page of Udacity.com.
现在我所在的是优达学城官方网站的招聘页面
Before I even open a job posting I can make inferences about the job.
在我打开一条招聘启事之前 我可以先对岗位要求进行推断
For example, Udacity is hiring in multiple countries,
比如 优达学城面向多个国家/地区进行招聘
so their products and programs are international.
所以他们的产品和课程是国际性的
I'd make sure to include in my resume or cover letter, any past experiences
那我就需要确保在我的简历或求职信中 包含我之前在任何国际团队
working with international teams and how I resolved conflicts that may come up
工作的经验 以及是如何解决跨不同时区协助中
from logistics in collaborating across different time zones, for example.
可能会遇到的物流问题
I also see words like community, partner, and mentorship a lot.
我还频繁地看到社区、合作伙伴及导师等词
That tells me Udacity is looking to build a worldwide community for
从这些可以得知 优达学城正在尝试为学生建立一个
its students.
全球社区
So I want to include in my application my passion for connecting people.
所以我要在简历中包含对建立人际网络的兴趣
I think I have a pretty clear idea about what's important to Udacity, but
我想我已经非常清楚优达学城看重的方面了
sometimes it's not clear immediately what a company is looking for.
但有时候可能无法立即搞清楚一个公司的期望
Browsing through the rest of the website usually helps.
这时候就需要浏览一下网站上的其他部分
Now, I'm on the home page and the words that pop out as I'm scrolling down are,
现在 我在网站的首页 随着我往下滚动出现的词汇有
innovation, student community, industry-recognized, data, mobile,
创新、学生社区、受行业认可、数据、移动
face-to-face, job-ready.
面对面、做好了工作准备
This helps me answer the question that I will want to address in my cover letter,
这帮助我回答了我想在自己的求职信中解决的问题
and will definitely be asked in an interview.
而且这个问题一定会在面试中问到
Why do you want to work at Udacity?
你为什么想在优达学城工作？
I may answer that I want to use my skills to help make online education
我可以回答说我想运用自己的技能让在线教学
more personable by connecting students to real people or make sure Udacity
更个性化 比如连接学生与真人讲师 或者确保优达的
curriculum not only teaches students but helps them get a job in emerging field.
课程不只是教授学生知识 而且帮助他们在新兴领域找到工作
This exercise took only a couple minutes but was really insightful.
这个方法只需花费几分钟 但却可以提供很多的见解
Before doing this, I may have assumed Udacity's mission was to
在此之前 我可能以为优达的使命是
produce quality content with top tech companies.
为顶级技术公司生产高质量的内容
Sure, that's a goal, but their mission seems to be about making education
当然 这也是其目标之一 但现在看来他们的使命是将教育
accessible worldwide and making sure that education helps students get jobs.
全球化 并确保通过教育帮助学生找到工作
Being able to connect to a company's mission is the difference between being
是否认同公司的使命具有重要的影响 它决定了你是否只是
qualified for the job and landing the job offer.
符合岗位要求还是能够赢得工作机会
You may also want to pursue jobs that you may not have the experience or
有时候 你可能想应聘自己没有经验或
background for.
相关背景的职位
Showing that you understand what's important to the company and
展示出你了解公司看重的方面并且
that you're going to do everything you can to help drive the mission
你会尽全力帮助驱动公司使命的实现
makes the employer more inclined to take a chance on you and hire you anyway.
会使雇主更有可能考虑你并最终雇佣你
That worked for me.
我就是这样的例子
At one of my first jobs, my boss told me that I had the least
在第一次应聘某个职位时 雇主告诉我在面试的所有人中
amount of experience out of everyone they interviewed.
我的经验最少
However, I was so excited about the work they were doing that she was confident I
但是 我对他们所做的工作非常认同 她坚信
would be valuable to the organization and she hired me.
我一定会成为组织宝贵的一份子 所以她选择了我